I'm Jimmy, I'm the host of the show.
Very kind, thanks for joining us here in sunny Los Angeles, where we are, I
wouldn't go so far as to say we are celebrating Earth Day, but we're observing
it.
It is Earth Day today.
At this point, with all we've done to this planet, humans celebrating Earth Day is
like Kanye celebrating Hanukkah.
It doesn't matter at all.
Republicans in the House today, they were supposed to have a vote on a bill
that would narrow protections for endangered species.
On Earth Day, they were doing this.
Fortunately, the vote was postponed.
We will kill the turtles on the flag day instead.
But this planet is home to at least 8 million different species.
Did you know that, Guillermo?
No, I did not.
And some scientists believe the true number could be more than a trillion.
There is so much to learn about our animal friends.
And in studying them, we learn a lot about ourselves.
For instance, researchers from Australia and Sweden are doing a study about drug pollution in
the water, and they found that salmon that are exposed to cocaine swim nearly twice
as far as those that do not have a coke problem.
The study found that the cocaine salmon swim around 20% faster, and also, they never
shut up.
I want to know more about these researchers, because let's see what happens if we
give salmon cocaine is one of the cocanius thoughts I've ever heard.
We are living in a golden age of wild animals being exposed to illicit substances,
which is a nice segue into the case of Kash Patel, our future former director
of the FBI, who's getting hammered this week over a report that says he's been
getting hammered on the job.
Patel on Monday filed a lawsuit against The Atlantic for a story they published that
alleged, among other things, that the director's, quote, episodes of excessive drinking have alarmed his
colleagues and is a recurring source of concern across the government.
Patel denies this, and not just categorically, maniacally.
He announced that he is suing The Atlantic for $250 million.
The Atlantic issued a statement responding to that.
They said, we stand by our reporting on Kash Patel, and we will vigorously defend
The Atlantic and our journalists against this meritless lawsuit.
Patel claims the allegations are completely false, a hit piece, but the journalist who wrote
the story, her name is Sarah Fitzpatrick, says she spoke to more than two dozen
people, including current and former FBI officials.
Her version of the story makes it sound like Patel was blacked out more than
the president's name in the Trump-Epstein files.
And this comes the same week that a federal judge dismissed the defamation lawsuit
Patel filed against a former FBI agent who said he has been, quote, visible at
nightclubs far more than he has been on the seventh floor of the Hoover building
where they work.
One of the allegations in the story is that Patel's been so worried about losing
his job around two weeks ago, he had some trouble logging into his computer and
freaked out because he assumed he'd been fired and they locked him out.
The article said he called at least nine people to tell them he had been
let go.
Then it turned out it was an IT issue and he got back in.
So Patel angrily denied that story.
And he proved that the old adage, the best way to address rumors of erratic
behavior is to hold an even more erratic press conference.
Did you communicate with anyone that you thought you were fired after you were unable
to log into the...
The problem with you and your report...
Don't cut me off.
You asked the question.
Straightforward question.
The problem with you and your baseless reporting is that is an absolute lie.
Simple, straightforward question.
Did you talk to anybody about whether you thought you were fired?
The simple answer to your question is you are lying.
I was never locked out of my systems.
Anybody who says- Your lawsuit says the opposite.
Anyone that says the opposite is lying.
Thank you.
The lawsuit that you filed says that.
Stop.
You're being extraordinarily rude.
You know they don't like that in that administration.
Now keep in mind, the guy asking the question, that wasn't the reporter who wrote
the Atlantic story.
It was another reporter just asking if the story was true.
And also, there is a specific account of Patel not being able to access his
computer in the lawsuit he filed against The Atlantic.
His own lawyers put it in there, so that did happen, but you can't ask
about that because it's extraordinarily rude.
Can you say definitively that you have not been intoxicated or absent during your tenure
as FBI director?
I can say unequivocally that I never listen to the fake news mafia, and when
they get louder, it just means I'm doing my job.
So, no, then, is the answer?
He's so wound up.
He's so angry.
If only there were some kind of a bottle of, like, a magic liquid he
could drink, and it would calm his nerves in some way.
Give him a little buzz or something.
And then we have our Secretary of Health, RFK Jr., who famously puts everything
but alcohol in his body.
Kennedy testified before two Senate committees today.
He had a grilling from Republicans and Democrats, including Senator Elizabeth Warren, who cut him
like a raccoon penis.
He claims that Trump Rx has reduced prices by as much as 600 percent.
600 percent, which I think means companies should be paying you to take their drugs.
President Trump has a different way of calculating.
There's two ways of calculating percentage.
If you have a $600 truck and you reduce it to 10, that's a 600% reduction.
You have to understand, President Trump has a different way of calculating from the rest.
Who are you going to believe, him or math?
Have you ever bankrupted a casino?
I don't think so.
Now, the actual math is 98%, not 600%.
but let's not get caught up in semantics.
Let's just be quiet and listen to Robert Kennedy breathe.
Among the many that you described in your testimony,
in that context, in your testimony, you identified nutrition as a bedrock of health and
one of the primary levers for treating and preventing chronic disease.
Education is an incredible start.
I don't think it was very long ago that there was probably very little nutrition
taught in medical school.
And now we are encouraging that to be a focal point.
You understand, our Secretary of Health is dying before our eyes.
And no one is doing anything about it.
We are on day nine now of Trump's blockade of the blockade at the Strait
of Hormuz.
Every day this goes on, the prices go up, and not just on oil and
gas.
Carex, the world's largest manufacturer of condoms, may have to raise their prices by 20
to 30 percent because of supply chain issues caused by the war.
The price of condoms will affect the straight of Hormuz and the gays of Hormuz,
too.
eat them.
Carrick said there are vessels filled with condoms that cannot get to their
destinations where they are desperately needed, specifically Nick Cannon's house.
But is there any metaphor more fitting than Donald Trump screwing us without condoms?
because he won't pull out.
I mean, yesterday,
Trump added an extension to the ceasefire, and then today he said there's no time
frame on a deal with Iran, which is interesting because from day one, some guy
has been telling us over and over that it's over.
We have right from the beginning, we projected four to five weeks.
I think you'll see it's going to be a short term excursion.
We're going to have a much safer world as soon as it's finished.
It's going to be finished pretty quickly.
Most people say it's already been won.
You know, you never like to say too early you won.
We won.
We won the bet in the first hour it was over.
When are you going to know when it's over?
When I feel it.
OK.
Pulling up my bones.
A couple of weeks and won't be much longer.
You know, I don't like to say this.
We've won this.
This war has been won.
We've already won the war.
Militarily, we've totally won the war.
I do see a deal in Iran.
Mr.
President.
Could be soon.
I would say that within two weeks, maybe two weeks, maybe three, We are on
track to complete all of America's military objectives shortly, very shortly.
It could end very quickly, the war.
We win regardless.
We've defeated them militarily.
Well, you keep saying was.
Is this war over?
I think it's close to over, yeah.
I mean, I view it as very close to over.
I think what he's trying to say is the war might not be over, but
he is over the war.
You know, speaking of over, the New York Mets have the second highest payroll
in, I think, the history of baseball.
And they've also now, as of the time we are taping this show, lost 12
games in a row.
It's their longest losing streak in more than 40 years.
The last time the Mets were this bad, half the team had jerry curls and
the other half had mullets.
I am a Mets fan.
And stupidly, I once again, I stupidly had high hopes for this season.
as did many fans.
Steve Gelbs, the Mets field reporter, did his best last night to reverse the curse.
But I have to say, sorry, Steve, I don't care how big a joint you
roll for those children.
It's not going to help.
And this is interesting.
Follow along with this, because on April 9th, the mayor of New York, Bob Donnie,
showed up at Citi Field.
He hugged Mr.
Mett and Mrs.
Mett.
And since then, they've done nothing but lose.
And many in the right wing media are now blaming him.
The New York Mets, they are on an 11-game losing streak, including, oh, right after
the mayor met and hugged the team mascot, Mr.
Met.
Socialist Mayor Zoran Mamdani can't do anything right.
Do you blame Mamdani for the losing streak?
Yes, absolutely.
He's got a lot of New Yorkers that are really upset.
New Yorkers are calling it the curse of Mayor Mambino.
We need an exorcism in sports.
The only way to reverse this, Sean, is President Trump has to come to a
Mets game.
That's right.
The only way to stop a loser is with an even bigger loser.
I looked into this.
I think I might have it figured out.
This has nothing to do with the mayor.
Something changed at Citi Field this season.
For the first time in Mets history, they installed partitions between the urinals.
They used to have a trough.
You just line up.
But now there are dividers.
As if we weren't already divided enough, they've added dividers to the men's room.
We did some research, and I think I found the source of why this happened.
Two years ago, February 1st, 2024, the Mets posted, we are proud to celebrate Black
History Month throughout the month of February.
And the top comment under that post was from a James70889886.
He wrote, please put walls between the urinals in the men's bathrooms at Citi Field.
This is 2024.
Men feel uncomfortable and don't pee next to men urinating.
fights can happen when men look at the penis of other men.
Do you find that to be true, Guillermo?
I don't think so.
I guess they, anyway, they listened to James and they put in his precious wiener
shields and now we lost 12 games in a row.
So I'm calling on Mets team owner Steve Cohen to tear down those urinal walls.
And I'm saying they do.
I know maybe it can't happen immediately, but Mets fans, when you're at the game,
I want you to squeeze between those dividers, double up, triple up, whatever you have
to do.
Hopefully the Mets broke the streak tonight against the Twins.
Mets hosted Minnesota.
We're hosting the Minnesota governor tonight, Tim Walz.
Tim Walls is a very regular guy, but Minnesota, when it comes to politics, is
a colorful state.
They had Jesse the Body Ventura as governor, Al the Body Franken was their senator,
and now one of their candidates to succeed Tim Walls is our old friend, the
My Pillow Man, Mike Lindell.
Into our country, most of them break a law within the first three months.
Most of them, we're on TV here, please.
We're on TV, please.
What are you serving him with?
I'm not accepting it.
What are you trying to serve him with?
We're on TV, please.
Okay.
So somehow, CPAC, the Conservative Political Action Conference, endorsed Mike Lindell as their candidate, who
is a, if you don't know, a former crack addict, self-made pillow millionaire, turned soon-to-be
bankrupt election denier.
But despite his many legal, financial, and perhaps mental issues, Mike managed to secure an
endorsement not just from CPAC, but also from himself.
Hello there, it's Mike Lindell.
You know who.
I got thousands of pillows and a gun under each one.
Next year, Minnesotans face the most important election since the 97 Lake Hiawatha wet sweatshirt
contest.
I voted for Pudgy Peggy.
But in 20-odd-26, we gotta get a new governor.
And that's why I'm endorsing a great American who overcame a whole lot of hardships
and head injuries.
Me, Mike Lindell, for governor.
Nobody knows Mike Lindell better than me because I am him.
I know how he thinks I know what makes him tick It's a pacemaker On
account of a bungee accident Where Mike's organs got all mumbo jumbo I even know
where Mike hides his stash Of ivermectin and hydroxychloroquine For when the bovine herpes flares
up And Mike wants me to tell you That for a limited time Everything in
his medicine cabinet Is buy two get one free Use promo code hydro Hydroxyl Hydroxyl
Pills!
Don't just take my word about me for it.
I got plenty endorsements, like my sleep paralysis demon.
And four out of five of the voices in my head.
Number five tells me to start fires at the River Hills Mall.
Watch it burn!
Burn it down!
Now, voice of my community!
And this election, no crooked voting machines.
You want to vote for me?
You got to snowshoe to an old bar.
tell a joke to a goat, then drop a pine cone in the voting bucket,
the way the founding fathers meant for us to.
So, vote for me.
Glad Neil Ekham.
Who the hell put this upside down so wrong?
Wrong house again.
Wrong house!
Who are you?
Paid for by me, even though I ain't got no money left.
Ah, my janglies!
They got stagged!
He's got my vote.
We've got a good show tonight.
Governor Tim Walz is here with us tonight from Las Vegas.
Frankie Perez is sitting in with the Kletones.
And we'll be right back with Adam Scott.